https://www.kosher.com/privacy-policy

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us and we are committed to protecting the privacy of your information.
Kosher.com will use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this Privacy Policy.
Information About You
When you voluntarily provide it, we collect personal information in the course of interacting with the site. When using the site, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information such as your name, address, or e-mail address. If you share a recipe or an article with a friend, you must provide the name and e-mail address of the recipient. Contact information, such as name, email and phone number, and demographic information, may be gathered from our visitors from information requests or other forms.
We may use the information you give us to provide services to you, at your request. We may use it to communicate with you through periodic messages regarding services, events, and other information and notices. We may use it for confirmation of registrations, or other actions you take on our site, and for related customer service needs. We use information you provide about others to enable us to send them your recipes, articles you choose to share, or other services. We only use contact information to send information requested or to contact users as necessary.
We do not sell, rent, swap or otherwise share our mailing lists with external organizations. Any personal information you provide to Kosher.com will not be disseminated to third parties outside of our organization.
We also may collect information that is not personally identifiable, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), the IP address you are using, and the domain name of your Internet service provider. We may use this information to analyze the design and functionality of our site in order to make site improvements. We may use such information in the aggregate to analyze site usage.
Our website does not automatically collect any individually identifiable information, such as email addresses, from visitors.
We pledge that we will never willfully sell, trade, rent, disclose, or make available personally identifiable information about you to any third party without first receiving your permission, except when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, or to protect the rights or property of Kosher.com.
Cookies
Our site makes limited use of cookies. "Cookies" are small text files that are stored on a local computer hard drive that contain information related to your use of a site. A cookie can't read data off of your computer hard disk or read cookie files created by other Web sites. Cookies do not damage your system. Cookies help websites provide visitors with customized features. Our site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, location, and for other purposes. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our site may be diminished and some features may not work as intended.
Links
We provide links to other Web sites that we believe you will find useful or relevant. Kosher.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Email Subscription Lists
Kosher.com offers an email subscription list to its visitors that you can opt in to. We will never subscribe you to any mailing list without your request or agreement. If you are subscribed to any lists, we provide the ability to opt-out of receiving these communications from us by following the instruction listed in the email. We will never pass on your email address to a third party or send you spam.
Contacting Us
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us via our contact page.
NEWSLETTER
Subscribe to kosher.com
For the latest and trendiest recipes!
Subscribe to kosher.com
For the latest and trendiest recipes!
BACK TO TOP
